♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hello, I'm Brian Griffin.
And I'm Stewie Griffin.
A few years ago, we did an
episode called "Viewer Mail"
where you, our fans,
wrote in and suggested ideas
for new episodes.
Well, it's ten years later, but
you're still sending in ideas.
Uh, to Rashad in Little Rock,
we wanna let you know
we kicked around idea, "Make the
Baby Go Wild" for a while,
couldn't really find
an angle on it.
Here's one from
Lee Mills of Iowa.
Lee writes: "Dear Family Guy,
was your show based on anything?"
That's a great question, Lee.
In fact, Family Guy is based
on an American television series
called The Simpsons.
(chuckles) Actually, Family Guy,
much like The Office,
is based on a British series
called Chap of the Manor.
Let's watch.
(farting)
ANNOUNCER:
We now return to Britain's
most popular game show...
BRITISH AUDIENCE:
Wheel... of... Politeness!
Do go ahead, then.
Oh, no, you first.
Wouldn't dream of it.
Too kind, really, I insist.
Wouldn't be proper of me.
I appreciate your courtesy.
Likewise.
Well, we're all out of time.
Join us same time tomorrow
if it's not entirely
inconvenient for you.
If so, of course,
we do understand
and we do apologize in advance.
This has all been an imposition.
I'm so dreadfully sorry.
Sorry! Sorry.
Sorry.
Sorry, everyone!
All right, kids, enough telly.
I hope everyone's peckish
for some boiled lamb shank.
None for me, Lydia.
I'm meeting me mates
down at the pub.
Again? But Neville,
you spend all your time
down at the Fox and Pig
and Dog and Wolf and Cat
and Fiddle and
Whistle and Cock.
And that's where
you're wrong.
The Fox and Pig and Dog
and Wolf and Cat
and Fiddle and Whistle and Cock
is for tossers.
We're meetin' at the Dog and Cat
and Bull and Whistle
and Fiddle and Cock
and Pig and Wolf and Carriage
and Fife and Other Wolf!
But I need you to stay and have
a chat with Collingsworth.
I found him with another fag
in his mouth this morning.
Oh, is that right?
So you fancy fags, do you?
Well, here.
Have a whole carton of fags!
I just want a comely lass
to look upon me with favour.
I look on you with favour.
I look on all of you
with favour.
Shut up, British Meg.
(Texas accent)
Look at Lydia.
What a two-bit Wichita whore.
One of these days,
she's gonna wake up killt.
Ah, matricide.
Yet another of
your childhood whims.
No, it ain't. I'm gonna follow
through with...
Wait, why'd you say it
like that?
Cutaway, sir?
Yes, that's good then.
Friends, family,
and characters random
To bring you joy
and laughter in tandem
To divert and dazzle
is our intention
So sit back, relax,
and enjoy our invention.
Ah, I love summer.
Good evening, Billingsbury.
I'm Clive Crowley.
Coming up: a man with a gun
and two bullets
has taken over the city
of Manchester.
But first, our top story
tonight: Her Majesty, the Queen,
will be passing through
our very town tomorrow.
With details, we now go live
to Indian reporter,
Tricia Dasgupta.
Oh, my golly,
there is much commotion.
Thank you, Tricia.
After the interval,
find out which 12 football teams
tied tonight.
The Queen's comin'
to Billingsbury?
That's bloody sweet!
You know, I'm actually a
relation of the royal family.
You most certainly are not.
Where would you
get that idea?
Me mum used to claim
she was a Windsor.
And I always heard my Nana talk
about how she took a duke.
Must've been a difficult
marriage, too,
'cause every afternoon
she'd be belly-achin'
about her bloody duke.
I think you just had
a gross grandmother.
No, I'm quite sure of it.
And to prove it,
I'm gonna nick
one of the Queen's hairs
during her visit tomorrow.
And when the DNA proves a match,
you'll see I'm royalty.
The Queen, eh?
I'd like to mash my banger
in her blood pudding.
Googity. Googity. Glop.
Hello, lads.
Oh, hello, Seamus.
Right fine performance
at the cricket match today.
Aye. I was spirited to have you
down there watching me.
P.A. ANNOUNCER:
Well, it's a brilliant day
for a long and
confusing game of cricket.
The field is teeming
with men in helmets
who don't seem like
they need helmets,
and men not in helmets
who seem like they probably
should be wearing helmets.
Oh, he's batted it
clear out of the stadium.
Is that good? We don't know,
but it's what we do!
Y-Yay!
Boo!
Oh my goodness, the Queen is
going to be here presently.
This is oh-so-exciting!
My favorite part
before the Queen arrives
is yelling "wanker"
at Prince Charles as he passes.
Wanker!
I know, I know.
Yes, I know. Yes.
Wanker!
You're a wanker!
Right, quite right.
Spot on. He's got it.
I say, a lot of people have
turned out to see the Queen.
Should make for a grand day.
Hey, watch it there!
Good show, old chap.
Well played.
Here she comes!
(crowd cheering)
Very well.
Time for action.
A lock of the Queen's hair
shall soon be mine.
Here she comes.
Have at it then.
Crikey! This is a haircut
fit for a queen!
Oh, bloody hell!
All right, time for Plan B.
Let's go!
I'm not going any lower.
Well, Father,
you gave it a good go.
Oh, we're not done yet.
Come on!
(tires squeal)
Queen! Queen! Give me
some of your hair!
Come on, Queen!
Don't be a bitch!
Get us away
from that lunatic!
(tires squeal)
She's heading into that tunnel!
(crashing, horse neighs)
GUARD (screaming):
Dear God! The Queen's dead!
(both whistling)
All right, Collingsworth,
I got a hair.
Now, just walk away casual-like
and we're in the clear.
Oh, no!
Here come the coppers!
("Yakkity Sax" playing)
(inhales deeply)
Bugger.
Well, it turns out
I'm not royalty.
Shame about the Queen, though.
Yeah, I reckon she's with
Jesus Christ in heaven now.
(spits)
(metallic ding)
Well, I'm just happy our
family is safe and sound
back in our cozy row house.
Row house.
(thunder rumbling)
TV ANNOUNCER:
We now return
to The Comedy Central Roast
of Robin Williams.
Aw, man, Robin Williams
is my favorite!
He must be getting recognized
for all his contributions
to show business.
I don't think
that's what a roast is.
Robin, as a comic, it's an honor
to be up here roasting you.
As a moviegoer, I want
to punch you in the face.
(laughter)
Oh, that's funny.
Advocate violence.
And let's face it, Mork.
You're getting Nanu-Na-old!
(laughs)
(laughter)
Stop it! You stop it!
Robin Williams has a manic gift
that gladdens a sad world
and all he asks in return
is our unceasing attention!
How can you allow this?!
Robin Williams has given us
nothing but joy!
I wish everyone
was Robin Williams!
(thunder rumbling)
(electric sizzling)
Boy, that looks enticing.
(thunder rumbling)
(electric sizzling)
Yeah, this is nice.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
You were in a coma, and then I
kissed you, and you woke up.
(mumbles)
Like two days later.
Anyway, all your
numbers are normal.
What numbers?
No idea.
Well, congratulations.
You're gonna be just fine.
(electric buzzing)
Oh, my God!
You're...
You're Robin Williams!
Ding! Thank you for playing
"That's Obvious!"
Tell him what he's won, Cletus!
(hick accent): Money!
(normal): Ho-ho! Money.
Or as the Republicans
call it,
(imitating witch):
Mine!
(laughs)
I hope this is covered
by your HMO.
I was covered once by
an HMO in San Francisco.
I Haight my Ashbury
in these jeans!
Ding-ding, Rice-A-Roni!
Ah! You got all those
references in there!
Of course now everyone
can afford health care
because of Obama.
Yeah, you want a Band-Aid?
No problem, turkey.
Come on down to Obama-Mart!
The price is free,
but yo ass better vote for me.
Ha! Political
with a twist.
It's funny from the news!
What's going on in here?
You gotta check this out!
It's Robin Williams!
Ho-ho! A nurse
is a nurse, of curse.
Up yours, Wilbur.
Oh, my God!
Everyone I touch
turns into Robin Williams!
Yess! Peter Sweet Cheeks
Griffin-uh!
You have been given
the power from god-uh!
Ho-ho! Ho-ho!
Ho-ho!
(laughing)
I will be so responsible
with this.
Thanks, guys!
Ho-ho!
Bye!
See you, Peter!
Y'all come back now, y'hear?
(chuckles)
It's Patch Adams Robin.
He cures stuff the fun way,
not the medicine way.
So, somehow the lightning
gave your dad
the power to turn anyone
I touch into Robin Williams.
Peter, did Dr. Hartman say
how long this was gonna last?
There is no more
Dr. Hartman, Lois.
He's Robin Williams now.
Bet you kids never thought
your dad
would have superpowers, huh?
Peter!
Ho-ho! You pat my back, I pat yours,
and Pat Robertson
pats Mr. Happy.
(Southern accent): Yayuss! Praise
Jesus with your Visa card!
Max it out
on the Lord, people!
Oh, boy!
And that's the second
Southern preacher one.
Look, Brian! Meg is
one of the sensitive,
bearded Robin Williams
characters.
Ha!
You think that's funny, chief?
Well, I...
My wife is dead.
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
She's dead, chief.
Ho-ho! Dead.
The Grateful Dead. Please
do not take the brown acid.
It will turn you
into a Martian.
Take me to your wiener.
Ho-ho!
We're (bleep).
("Rockin' Robin"
by Bobby Day playing)
♪ ♪
♪ He rocks in the treetop
all a day long ♪
♪ Hoppin' and a-boppin'
and a-singin' the song ♪
♪ All the little birds
on Jaybird Street ♪
♪ Love to hear the robin
goin' tweet-tweet-tweet ♪
♪ Rockin' robin,
tweet-tweet-tweet. ♪
I don't know, Peter.
This all seems kind of creepy.
What do you mean?
This is great!
Everyone's hilarious now!
What do you think, Quagmire?
What? I can't hear a thing
over this noise.
What?!
This is unbearable!
I think I got just the thing
to cheer you up, Joe.
I know I said I was a leg man,
but this is ridiculous. Ho!
I feel like a testicle
on steroids.
Honey, I shrunk my nuts!
Ho! Ha!
Ho-ho! I'm a
San Francisco pirate.
I Haight my Ashbury
in these jeans!
A lot of the material
is repeated.
Mmm, Lois,
your torso is
so broad and solid.
(spits, coughs)
Ah! You're not Lois!
I can hear you!
I'm not deaf!
I don't believe that's
real sign language!
Brian, this is
a disaster!
I turned everyone
into Robin Williams!
You gotta help me!
Yo-yo-yo! Peter G.
What's happening,
dawg?
Oh, Sideways Hat Robin.
Dear God, no!
(kettle whistles)
♪ Gonna have some hot tea,
baby, this morning! ♪
(yells)
Run, Forrest, run!
All right, Rupert,
all we have to do
is act like Robin Williams,
and he'll think
we've already changed.
Ho-ho! Scattered
stream of references!
Lots of energy! One good one
for every ten! Ho-ho!
Damn these hands!
Mwah!
Vell, I haven't been
to temple in a while!
Ah!
Ladies and gentleman,
The Doors!
(screaming)
Ho-ho! Jogging!
Running on empty! Ho-ho!
Run, Forrest, run!
ALL:
Ho-ho! Ho-ho! Ho-ho!
Ho-ho! I'm a Mercedes!
Und vere are your papers?
Are you from
East or Vest Berlin?
(a la John Wayne):
Vell, I'm from Vest Berlin, pilgrim.
(sobbing)
Shut up!
(yelling)
(sobbing)
Ho-ho! Ho-ho!
Stop riffing!
Jump, Forest, jump!
Must be a leap
year, ho-ho!
Time to lose
some weight, dearie?
No... more... comedy.
Guys, will you please
settle down?
Can we, can we settle down,
please?
Every... everyone.
Everyone, can I have
your attention?
Oh, Captains! My Captains!
I have an announcement to make:
You are all free!
You have been fired
from the school.
Vietnam is over.
The hospital is closing.
Will Hunting is all better.
It's not your fault.
Shut up. Seriously, shut up.
Please, you are done here.
Go and spread your comedy
to all corners of this country.
Wait, not you five.
I'm gonna keep you for...
an experiment.
Ho-ho! Eggs!
Who came first, the chicken
or the porn star?
Ho-ho!
The Porn Identity!
Who am I? Oh, yeah!
The pizza man!
Baka-chikka-bwow-bwow!
Ho-ho! Ho-ho!
Peter, can you pass
the coffee?
Sure, Brian the dog.
Anything for my family.
Coffee now.
Here we go, here we go.
I guess Disney wouldn't let us
do the Aladdin one.
LOIS:
Stewie, rise and shine.
Good morning, Stewie.
(bleep) you.
You ready for the day, sweetie?
Oh, someone needs
a diaper change.
Are you proud
of yourself?
That this
is what you do?
Is this a dime?
Did you swallow a dime?
Yeah, wipe it off
and put it back in your purse,
you white trash hen.
There we go.
Who's my clean little boy?
(Stewie laughing)
Ugh! Your roots
are ridiculous.
I'm gonna grab
your hair 'cause
I like grabbing stuff.
Okay. Okay, Stewie, let go.
Let, let go, Stewie.
Let go of Mommy's hair.
When I grow up, I'm
never gonna call you.
I'm gonna be busy
with my job and my family.
You'll be nothing.
Stewie, I want you
to have my ring.
It's one of my most
important possessions,
and I want you to have it.
Okay, red flag.
Red flag, everybody!
Hey, Stewie,
wanna go down the slide?
STEWIE:
Um...
What's the matter?
Ya never been down
the slide before?
(scoffs) Yeah, like,
like a thousand times.
Just done it so much
I'm bored with it, that's all.
All right, I guess
we're doing this.
Whoa.
Come on down,
Stewie!
(hawks screeching)
This is crazy. This is crazy.
This is crazy.
All right, you can do this,
Stewie. Here we go.
(screams)
(thud)
Are you okay?
Yeah, that wasn't so bad.
You might wanna move.
That farting Polish kid
is coming down the slide.
(Stewie grunts)
(kid farts)
Ah, Pavel!
Hey, kid, come here.
I wanna see
if I can still smell
your mom's boobs on your mouth.
Why don't you go hump
a pile of garbage?
All right, here we go.
Classic.
(engine starts)
Uh-oh. (grunts)
Oh, God! Brian! Brian!
Guess I'm going for a ride.
Why are we stopping?
(squirrel chitters)
Oh, come on.
For God's sake, Brian.
It's just a squirrel.
BRIAN:
Yeah!
Oh, God!
(Stewie groans)
He can't hurt you anymore.
Hey there, little fella.
We sure got a lovely day for it,
don't we?
Stay away from
my brother's butt.
Okay, Stewie, let's get
that little face washed off.
Then you can play
with your bath toys, huh?
No, I hate getting
my face washed!
Oh, look!
It's just Mr. Frog!
Hello, Mr. Frog...
(spluttering)
My God, how the hell
do I keep falling for that?
Now you play with your toys
and I'll go get yo
a nice, fluffy towel.
Stewart Griffin, explorer,
adventurer,
skin-diving
international playboy.
(takes deep breath)
(Stewie growls, screams)
I'm swimming at night
'cause I'm a slut
and now I'm paying
the price for it.
(panting)
Hey, Stewie!
Wow, looks like you got
some cool bath toys in there.
Is it okay if I join ya?
No! (screams)
Hey, is that
my froggie butt cloth?
Okay, Stewie, bedtime's
in ten minutes.
I'll be right back.
Hmm. I think I have time
for a quickie.
Excuse me, Mr. Cobain.
Look, I know
you're depressed.
Made some bad choices
with women,
but there's another way.
Haagen-Dazs,
lots of Haagen-Dazs.
(whooshing)
Well, let's see if it worked.
Here we go.
Ha! You're still alive,
you fat (bleep).
Okay, Stewie, time for bed.
You want Mommy to read you
a night-night story?
Oh, how 'bout this one?
"Good Night, Town
from Footloose"?
LOIS:
Who is this book for?
(slurring): Hey, Lois.
I'm home from the Clam.
You know what that means.
STEWIE: You spent the last ten minutes
parked in front of the house
crying in your car?
Not now, Peter. I'm doing
story time with Stewie.
Yeah, scram, Drinky.
I got a story.
It's about the little penis
that could.
It thinks it can, it thinks...
In fact, it's pretty sure
it can.
It-It, it's gonna.
Hey, am I gonna have
to handle this?
Do you want me
Peter, just go wait
in the bedroom.
I'll be right there.
Fine, but if I gotta pee first,
this night's gonna be ruined.
Ruined.
Good night, sweetie.
Mommy loves you.
(Stewie yawns)
(rhythmic thudding)
Huh?
(both grunting)
It's big, isn't it?
Yes, Peter.
It's very big.
Yeah, it's big.
Oh, God, yes!
Ah, yes...
Ah, yeah.
Oh, you're gonna use that thing,
good. I love you so much.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru